<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<NewsApiData xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns="http://mynamespace/test/">
  <Status>ok</Status>
  <TotalResults>30</TotalResults>
  <Articles>
    <Article>
      <Source>
        <Id>associated-press</Id>
        <Name>Associated Press</Name>
      </Source>
      <Author>Christopher Rugaber</Author>
      <Title>Shutdown leaves a mark on an already-struggling economy, from lost paychecks to canceled flights - AP News</Title>
      <Description>The longest federal government shutdown in U.S. history appears to be nearing an end, but not without leaving a mark on an already-struggling economy. About 1.25 million federal workers missed at least one or two paychecks. Thousands of flights have been canc…</Description>
      <Url>https://apnews.com/article/economy-impact-shutdown-snap-flights-trump-826406b1083b262cad78338bc99f103b</Url>
      <UrlToImage>https://dims.apnews.com/dims4/default/8575cc0/2147483647/strip/true/crop/5000x2813+0+261/resize/1440x810!/quality/90/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fassets.apnews.com%2F3a%2Ff5%2F12644fc5614bc818caafeee80fca%2F5f0516789dfe47b1a2b62c4264c6b437</UrlToImage>
      <PublishedAt>2025-11-12T01:30:00Z</PublishedAt>
      <Content>WASHINGTON (AP) The longest federal government shutdown in U.S. history appears to be nearing an end, but not without leaving a mark on an already-struggling economy. 
About 1.25 million federal wor… [+6796 chars]</Content>
    </Article>
    <Article>
      <Source>
        <Name>NPR</Name>
      </Source>
      <Author />
      <Title>Why flight disruptions could linger even after the government shutdown ends - NPR</Title>
      <Description>Airlines and aviation regulators warned that flight disruptions are likely to continue even after the government reopens. Thousands of flights have been cancelled as air traffic restrictions ramp up.</Description>
      <Url>https://www.npr.org/2025/11/11/nx-s1-5605538/air-traffic-control-flights-controllers-government-shutdown</Url>
      <UrlToImage>https://npr.brightspotcdn.com/dims3/default/strip/false/crop/4200x2363+0+0/resize/1400/quality/100/format/jpeg/?url=http%3A%2F%2Fnpr-brightspot.s3.amazonaws.com%2F05%2F07%2Fc05079db4d4c99b01e6792524acc%2Fap25315690999467.jpg</UrlToImage>
      <PublishedAt>2025-11-12T01:28:17Z</PublishedAt>
      <Content>WASHINGTON Flight disruptions are likely to continue even after the government reopens, airlines and aviation regulators warned, as airlines cancelled scores of flights on Tuesday.
The Federal Aviat… [+3064 chars]</Content>
    </Article>
    <Article>
      <Source>
        <Id>bloomberg</Id>
        <Name>Bloomberg</Name>
      </Source>
      <Author>Min-Jeong Lee, Kentaro Tsutsumi</Author>
      <Title>SoftBank’s Shares Dive After Nvidia Sale Spooks AI-Wary Market - Bloomberg.com</Title>
      <Description>SoftBank Group Corp.’s stock slid as much as 10% after the tech investor’s exit from AI chipmaker Nvidia Corp. spooked investors already nervous about climbing tech-sector valuations.</Description>
      <Url>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-11-12/softbank-s-shares-dive-after-nvidia-sale-spooks-ai-wary-market</Url>
      <UrlToImage>https://assets.bwbx.io/images/users/iqjWHBFdfxIU/i8YJNsHWEaBQ/v0/1200x800.jpg</UrlToImage>
      <PublishedAt>2025-11-12T00:50:00Z</PublishedAt>
      <Content>SoftBank Group Corp.s stock slid as much as 10% after the tech investors exit from AI chipmaker Nvidia Corp. spooked investors already nervous about climbing tech-sector valuations.
The Japanese com… [+376 chars]</Content>
    </Article>
    <Article>
      <Source>
        <Id>the-washington-post</Id>
        <Name>The Washington Post</Name>
      </Source>
      <Author>Dan Diamond, Rachel Roubein</Author>
      <Title>FDA taps oncology expert Pazdur as nation’s top drug regulator - The Washington Post</Title>
      <Description>Richard Pazdur, a longtime Food and Drug Administration employee, will lead its center that oversees over-the-counter medicines and the majority of prescription drugs.</Description>
      <Url>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/11/11/richard-pazdur-fda-center-for-drug-evaluation-research/</Url>
      <UrlToImage>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/7K3L4PE3ZMDNFVSYAKWA4YDBQE_size-normalized.jpg&amp;w=1440</UrlToImage>
      <PublishedAt>2025-11-12T00:16:00Z</PublishedAt>
      <Content>The Trump administration has named Richard Pazdur, a longtime oncology expert at the Food and Drug Administration, as the nations top drug regulator.
Pazdur will lead the agencys Center for Drug Eva… [+284 chars]</Content>
    </Article>
    <Article>
      <Source>
        <Name>BBC News</Name>
      </Source>
      <Title>Starbucks' barista strike could undermine its turnaround plan - BBC</Title>
      <Description>The coffee giant is returning to its roots to boost sales but labour tensions could derail the strategy.</Description>
      <Url>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c5ype4j07xpo</Url>
      <UrlToImage>https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/branded_news/8790/live/85bfe0b0-be6e-11f0-ab9d-83e1c35826e9.jpg</UrlToImage>
      <PublishedAt>2025-11-12T00:04:20Z</PublishedAt>
      <Content>Danielle Kaye,Business reporter and 
Natalie Sherman,Business reporter
Starbucks workers attend a rally as they go on a one-day strike outside a store in Buffalo, New York, US, November 17, 2022.
… [+5339 chars]</Content>
    </Article>
    <Article>
      <Source>
        <Name>New York Post</Name>
      </Source>
      <Author>Lisa Fickenscher</Author>
      <Title>Amazon cuts 700 jobs in NYC alone on quest to streamline by slashing 30,000 positions - New York Post</Title>
      <Description>“The size of the Amazon cuts remains a head scratcher given the battle for talent and [the] AI revolution in motion,” said Wedbush analyst Dan Ives.</Description>
      <Url>https://nypost.com/2025/11/11/business/amazons-massive-layoffs-include-nearly-700-terminations-in-nyc-state-department-of-labor/</Url>
      <UrlToImage>https://nypost.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2025/11/newspress-collage-ye1mtws80-1762897718821.jpg?quality=75&amp;strip=all&amp;1762879729&amp;w=1200</UrlToImage>
      <PublishedAt>2025-11-11T23:48:00Z</PublishedAt>
      <Content>Amazons massive October layoffs included 660 terminations in Manhattan, according to New York State government records.
The ax fell on nine office addresses affecting corporate employees only, Amazo… [+2797 chars]</Content>
    </Article>
    <Article>
      <Source>
        <Name>TrekMovie</Name>
      </Source>
      <Title>Paramount Outlines Expanded Film Slate And More Streaming Originals… But What About Star Trek? - TrekMovie.com</Title>
      <Description>David Ellison and his team spoke to investors about the future of the transformed company that owns Star Trek.</Description>
      <Url>https://trekmovie.com/2025/11/11/paramount-outlines-expanded-film-slate-and-more-streaming-originals-but-what-about-star-trek/</Url>
      <UrlToImage>https://trekmovie.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/newparamount-trek-head2.jpg</UrlToImage>
      <PublishedAt>2025-11-11T23:13:10Z</PublishedAt>
      <Content>This week will mark the first 100 days since David Ellison and his Skydance team took over Paramount. For the last three months what Paramount is up to has been a hot topic in Hollywood, Wall Street,… [+7727 chars]</Content>
    </Article>
    <Article>
      <Source>
        <Id>bloomberg</Id>
        <Name>Bloomberg</Name>
      </Source>
      <Author>Ian King</Author>
      <Title>AMD Predicts Accelerating Sales Growth Driven by Data Centers - Bloomberg.com</Title>
      <Description>Advanced Micro Devices Inc., Nvidia Corp.’s nearest rival in AI chips, predicted accelerating sales growth over the next five years, driven by strong demand for its data center products.</Description>
      <Url>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-11-11/amd-predicts-accelerating-sales-growth-driven-by-data-centers</Url>
      <UrlToImage>https://assets.bwbx.io/images/users/iqjWHBFdfxIU/i6JU_zKg_G24/v1/1200x800.jpg</UrlToImage>
      <PublishedAt>2025-11-11T22:59:09Z</PublishedAt>
      <Content>Advanced Micro Devices Inc., Nvidia Corp.s nearest rival in AI chips, predicted accelerating sales growth over the next five years, driven by strong demand for its data center products.
Annual reven… [+413 chars]</Content>
    </Article>
    <Article>
      <Source>
        <Id>associated-press</Id>
        <Name>Associated Press</Name>
      </Source>
      <Author>Stan Choe</Author>
      <Title>The Dow rallies 550 points to a record - AP News</Title>
      <Description>Most of Wall Street is rising, and the U.S. stock market is back to where it was before last week’s swoon. The S&amp;P 500 added 0.2% Tuesday after erasing a loss taken during the morning. The Dow Jones Industrial Average rallied 539 points, or 1.2%, and was on t…</Description>
      <Url>https://apnews.com/article/stocks-markets-shutdown-trump-rates-e6aea0a5dcacc6087c492a0537ed6c40</Url>
      <UrlToImage>https://dims.apnews.com/dims4/default/79bf897/2147483647/strip/true/crop/6000x3375+0+312/resize/1440x810!/quality/90/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fassets.apnews.com%2F91%2F08%2F5887bc5448f70f9b163b65ab1aac%2F3bc070a8baa74d46a96881fcbe112db6</UrlToImage>
      <PublishedAt>2025-11-11T22:49:00Z</PublishedAt>
      <Content>NEW YORK (AP) Most U.S. stocks rose on Tuesday and carried the market back to where it was before last weeks swoon.
The S&amp;amp;P 500 added 0.2% after erasing a loss taken during the morning. Its been… [+4841 chars]</Content>
    </Article>
    <Article>
      <Source>
        <Name>Fox Baltimore</Name>
      </Source>
      <Author>DANNY TOW | FOX45 NEWS</Author>
      <Title>Chick-Fil-A to test new menu item in Baltimore - WBFF</Title>
      <Description>Fast-food chain Chick-Fil-A is rolling out a new test menu item, and Baltimoreans will be among the first with a chance to try it.Starting December 1, select Ch</Description>
      <Url>https://foxbaltimore.com/news/local/chick-fil-a-test-new-menu-item-baltimore-chicken-waffles</Url>
      <UrlToImage>https://foxbaltimore.com/resources/media/e1eceda4-11ab-45c8-bd19-23e9f0245a99-thumb_13762.png</UrlToImage>
      <PublishedAt>2025-11-11T22:31:39Z</PublishedAt>
      <Content>(WBFF) Fast-food chain Chick-Fil-A is rolling out a new test menu item, and Baltimoreans will be among the first with a chance to try it.
Starting December 1, select Chick-Fil-A locations in Baltimo… [+660 chars]</Content>
    </Article>
    <Article>
      <Source>
        <Name>Investor's Business Daily</Name>
      </Source>
      <Title>Stock Market Today: Dow Surges As Shutdown End Nears; Buffett Stock Gets Hot (Live Coverage) - Investor's Business Daily</Title>
      <Description>Stock Market Today: The Dow Jones index rose Tuesday after the passage of the shutdown bill. Nvidia partner CoreWeave plunged on earnings.</Description>
      <Url>https://www.investors.com/market-trend/stock-market-today/dow-jones-sp500-nasdaq-shutdown-bill-nvidia-nvda-coreweave-crwv/</Url>
      <UrlToImage>https://www.investors.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/Stock-wallstreetflag-01-adobe.jpg</UrlToImage>
      <PublishedAt>2025-11-11T21:21:00Z</PublishedAt>
      <Content>Information in Investors Business Daily is for informational and educational purposes only and should not be construed as an offer, recommendation, solicitation, or rating to buy or sell securities. … [+1064 chars]</Content>
    </Article>
    <Article>
      <Source>
        <Name>KTVU San Francisco</Name>
      </Source>
      <Author>Aja Seldon</Author>
      <Title>San Francisco Muni driver asleep as speeding train tosses screaming riders - KTVU</Title>
      <Description>San Francisco Muni passengers screamed as they were jolted, some falling from their seats, when a light rail train traveled at an excessive speed while the driver dozed off to sleep, according to video footage.</Description>
      <Url>https://www.ktvu.com/news/muni-driver-falls-asleep-san-francisco-video</Url>
      <UrlToImage>https://images.foxtv.com/static.ktvu.com/www.ktvu.com/content/uploads/2025/11/1280/720/screenshot-2025-11-11-115542.png?ve=1&amp;tl=1</UrlToImage>
      <PublishedAt>2025-11-11T20:51:02Z</PublishedAt>
      <Content>SAN FRANCISCO - San Francisco Muni passengers screamed as they were jolted, some falling from their seats, when a light rail train traveled at an excessive speed while the driver dozed off to sleep, … [+2724 chars]</Content>
    </Article>
    <Article>
      <Source>
        <Id>cbs-news</Id>
        <Name>CBS News</Name>
      </Source>
      <Author>Mary  Cunningham</Author>
      <Title>A 107% U.S. import tax on Italian pasta could make your favorite spaghetti pricier — or hard to find - CBS News</Title>
      <Description>The Trump administration is considering a new import duty on 13 of Italy's largest pasta exporters, including Barilla and La Molisana.</Description>
      <Url>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/italian-pasta-antidumping-duties-imports-disappear-barilla/</Url>
      <UrlToImage>https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/11/b8d8867c-a9d4-492b-90dd-818509d32a36/thumbnail/1200x630/52c1355aae7b83b2d67f47ed2c2d8078/gettyimages-2246090417-1.jpg</UrlToImage>
      <PublishedAt>2025-11-11T20:19:14Z</PublishedAt>
      <Content>Americans may soon be paying more for their favorite Italian pasta brands — or even have trouble finding imported spaghetti — as the Trump administration eyes a new import duty on 13 of Italy's large… [+3216 chars]</Content>
    </Article>
    <Article>
      <Source>
        <Name>Teslarati</Name>
      </Source>
      <Author>Simon Alvarez</Author>
      <Title>Tesla Takedown group prepares anti-Elon Musk effort on November 15 - Teslarati</Title>
      <Description>Organizers also emphasized that</Description>
      <Url>https://www.teslarati.com/tesla-takedown-group-prepares-anti-elon-musk-effort-nov-15/</Url>
      <UrlToImage>https://www.teslarati.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/2048px-Tesla_Takedown_protest_in_Brooklyn_15131-1000x600.jpg</UrlToImage>
      <PublishedAt>2025-11-11T19:37:06Z</PublishedAt>
      <Content>Elon Musk recently amplified the thoughts of Morgan Stanley analyst Adam Jonas, who had insight into the “Muskonomy” of his potentially interconnected ventures, something that was proposed at the rec… [+3460 chars]</Content>
    </Article>
    <Article>
      <Source>
        <Name>Slashdot.org</Name>
      </Source>
      <Title>AI's $5 Trillion Cost Needs Every Debt Market, JPMorgan Says - Slashdot</Title>
      <Description>The furious push by AI hyperscalers to build out data centers will need about $1.5 trillion of investment-grade bonds over the next five years and extensive funding from every other corner of the market, according to an analysis by JPMorgan. From a report: "T…</Description>
      <Url>https://slashdot.org/story/25/11/11/1730232/ais-5-trillion-cost-needs-every-debt-market-jpmorgan-says</Url>
      <UrlToImage>https://a.fsdn.com/sd/topics/ai_64.png</UrlToImage>
      <PublishedAt>2025-11-11T17:22:25Z</PublishedAt>
      <Content>A third of the US stock market is in AI related business. The AI bubble pop will be more like an envelope collapse in a hot air balloon, ascending so quickly that you can't close the parachute and th… [+1037 chars]</Content>
    </Article>
    <Article>
      <Source>
        <Name>FDA.gov</Name>
      </Source>
      <Author>Office of Inspections and Investigations</Author>
      <Title>ByHeart Broadens Voluntary Recall While Investigation Continues - fda.gov</Title>
      <Description>[New York, NY] – ByHeart, a next-generation baby nutrition company, announced today that it is expanding its voluntary recall to include all batches of ByHeart Whole Nutrition Infant Formula cans and Anywhere Pack™ nationwide. This action is being taken in cl…</Description>
      <Url>https://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/byheart-broadens-voluntary-recall-while-investigation-continues</Url>
      <UrlToImage>https://www.fda.gov/themes/custom/preview/img/FDA-Social-Graphic.png</UrlToImage>
      <PublishedAt>2025-11-11T17:10:00Z</PublishedAt>
      <Content>Summary
Company Announcement Date:
November 11, 2025
FDA Publish Date:
November 11, 2025
Product Type:
Food &amp;amp; Beverages 
Foodborne Illness
Reason for Announcement:
Recall Reason Descript… [+3659 chars]</Content>
    </Article>
    <Article>
      <Source>
        <Id>cbs-news</Id>
        <Name>CBS News</Name>
      </Source>
      <Title>Wendy's to close hundreds of U.S. stores as low-income consumers cut back - CBS News</Title>
      <Description>Wendy's plans to close hundreds U.S. restaurants over the next few months amid spending cutbacks from its customers.</Description>
      <Url>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/wendys-closing-restaurants-hamburger-chain-closures/</Url>
      <UrlToImage>https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/08/30c36cb6-1813-4063-bf20-97e345f08960/thumbnail/1200x630/6723aa382910e0533adf02a126806b5e/gettyimages-2184086643.jpg</UrlToImage>
      <PublishedAt>2025-11-11T15:17:46Z</PublishedAt>
      <Content>Wendy's plans to close hundreds of U.S. restaurants in the coming months as revenue and profits decline, with the company citing cutbacks by lower-income consumers that it expects will persist throug… [+2520 chars]</Content>
    </Article>
    <Article>
      <Source>
        <Id>the-times-of-india</Id>
        <Name>The Times of India</Name>
      </Source>
      <Author>Aastha Raj</Author>
      <Title>Texas Roadhouse Veterans Day Deal 2025: Top Freebies, discounts and where to get them — All restaurant dea - The Economic Times</Title>
      <Description>As Americans commemorate Veterans Day 2025 on Tuesday, restaurants and service chains nationwide are offering free meals, discounts, and special deals to honor veterans and active-duty members of the military.</Description>
      <Url>https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/international/us/texas-roadhouse-veterans-day-deal-2025-top-freebies-discounts-and-where-to-get-them-all-restaurant-deals/articleshow/125250483.cms</Url>
      <UrlToImage>https://img.etimg.com/thumb/msid-125250514,width-1200,height-630,imgsize-11680,overlay-economictimes/articleshow.jpg</UrlToImage>
      <PublishedAt>2025-11-11T13:16:23Z</PublishedAt>
      <Content>As Americans observe Veterans Day 2025 on Tuesday, restaurants and service chains across the United States are rolling out free meals, discounts, and special offers to honour veterans and active-duty… [+3907 chars]</Content>
    </Article>
  </Articles>
</NewsApiData>